Contact

648217167 (Mobile) aitorruto@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aitor-ruiz (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PHP

JavaScript

Microsoft SQL Server

Certifications

Driver

Aitor Ruiz Torralbo

Web Developer Full Stack

Viladecans

Summary

My name is Aitor Ruiz Torralbo, I am a web developer from Viladecans, Barcelona, Spain born on March 14, 2001.

I have finished the upper cycle of web application development. My native languages are Spanish and Catalan and I have a lot of experience with English.

My goal is to improve my level and knowledge to create my own company in the future.

Experience

Audax Renovables

Web Developer

October 2021 - Present (8 months)

International websites (Spain and Poland).

Troubleshoot website problems.

Development of improvements.

Automation.

NIVEL Z

Web developer technician

November 2020 - April 2021 (6 months)

Viladecans, Cataluña, España

Web page design. SEO web positioning. Google Adwords SEM. Online marketing. On-line projects. Hosting.

Ayuntamiento de Viladecans Computer support technician November 2018 - April 2019 (6 months)

Viladecans, Cataluña, España

Hardware and software installation and repair. Network maintenance. Troubleshooting.

Education

CEFP Núria

Superior Technician in Web Application Development, Information Technology · (September 2019 - July 2021)

INS Torre Roja

Half cycle microcomputer systems and networks, Technology / Computer Hardware Technician · (September 2018 - July 2020)